https://www.pokersitesuk.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy – Poker Sites UK – How We Use Your Information
by Jack Jackob  |  July 16, 2018
You are always best advised to ensure that you are aware of the privacy policy that is in place on any websites you visit and make use of, and with that in mind below I present to you the privacy policy in place here on the Poker Sites UK website.
Making Contact with UsContentsMaking Contact with UsNewslettersThird Party Website LinksPosting Comments and FeedbackUpdates to Our Privacy Policy
We do offer a way for you to make contact with the team here at Poker Sites UK, and as such first and foremost we would like to bring to your attention that whenever you do make contact with us the email address you supply us with will only be used to reply to your email, and will not be sold on to any third party or used to send you out promotional offers or deals.
If you do wish to contact us for any reason then you will find out contact details listed on the Contact Us section of this website.
Newsletters
We may however invite you to sign up to our newsletters and if you do decide to do so then you will be sent out offers and deals and any relevant news updates we wish to bring to your attention.
The information you do supply us with when signing up to any newsletter will at all times only be used for its intended purpose, and you are able to unsubscribe from that newsletter at any time.
Third Party Website Links
To ensure that you will qualify for any bonuses offers or deals when clicking onto any of our website links or images we do track such users and so does the website you will be taken to by clicking onto those links.
Also be aware that any third party website you then arrive at will have their own unique privacy policy, set of terms and conditions and may also have their own unique cookie policies too, which you should always read through and familiarize yourself with.
Posting Comments and Feedback
At certain times you may be offered the opportunity of leaving comments or feedback on this website, and if so we will require you to register to make such comments and feedback.
By doing so any personal information you supply us with will be stored safely and securely at all times, and will not be sold on or given to any third party, unless we you have given us your permission to do so or if we are required by law to pass on that information
Updates to Our Privacy Policy
If at any time in the future we do make any alterations or updates to our privacy policy we will time stamp those changes on this section of our website, so that you can see when those changes were implemented and put into place.
This privacy policy was last updated on the 17th of July 2018.
ContactNews Home
About Us
Contact Us
Copyright &COPY 2017 - 2020 PokerSitesUK.com. All rights reserved.
